

506 / 65 Dudley Street, West Melbourne. VIC

+61 0433 702 302

www.jeanvera.com

github.com/jeanvera23

TECHNOLOGIES

Frontend

- ReactJS, ES6/ES2015, Firebase, GraphQL.
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, JSON, Restful API, JQuery, XML, datatables.js, d3.js, Google VIsion API.
- Bootstrap, Ulkit.
- Material Design.

Backend

- C#. ASP.Net
- Node.js
- PHP, PHPSpreadsheet, PHPMailer, mPDF.

Database

• SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL.

Other

 Github, Jira, Slack, Unity3D, construct2.

SKILLS

- Knowledgeable about mobile responsive design
- Great ability to work with a team
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Excellent communication skills
- Keen understanding of responsive design principles

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer, author of Material Design for Ulkit, and graduate of Software Engineering. More than 5 years commercial experience helping start-ups, small businesses, and agencies achieve high-quality web and mobile applications. Dedicated and organized team player with a strong professional ethic. Able and keen to be part of any project that the company may need.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

02/2019 - 08/2019

Amici Tech PTY LTD - Sydney

- Developed new web platform to obtain police check certificates
 - o Frontend: ReactJS, react-redux,axios
 - o Backend: ASP.Net
 - Database: SQL Server 2008 R2
- Installed and configured Microsoft Azure App Service Module.
- Managed code revision history using Github; used JIRA boards to manage spring tasks.

Full Stack Web Developer

06/2015 - 10/2018

Max Uhle German School - Peru

- Worked with agile team to create a new Learning Management Software including attendance, library, nursery and admission applications.
 - o Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, dataTables.js D3.js.
 - Backend: PHP, PostgreSQL, PHPMailer, mPDF, PhpSpreadsheet.
- Developed file upload utility in JQuery to save historical patient documents for psychological purposes.
- Developed a utility in Javascript to print student IDs.
- Developed a Mailing application for parents and students.

Full Stack Web Developer

12/2014 - 07/2015

Bisont Peru LLC - Peru

- Designed and developed efficient and maintainable software according to the clients' business objectives related to ecommerce platforms.
- Studying, evaluating, and proposing solutions to complex challenges for introducing new features for the existing projects.
- Assisted technical support specialist in the installation and configuration of software products (POS Workstations, Barcode scanners, printers, etc).
- Assisted in solving customer problems about the company's products.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR DEGREE

Software Engineering

Catholic University of Santa Maria 2010 – 2014

INTERESTS

- Software Development
- Educative Games
- VR/AR Development
- Photography
- Drones
- 3D printing
- Internet of Things

REFERENCES

References available on request

EXPERIENCE

Mobile Application Developer

Inka Studios Entertainment - Peru

04/2014 - 12/2014

- Designed and developed games using Unity3D for Android and iOS
 - Backend: C#, Facebook API, Google Sign-In, InAppPurchase, SQLite.
- Installing and configuring smartphones and mobile emulators to create the working environment.
- Studying new opportunities for mobile applications in the market.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Material Design for Ulkit

2019

Material Design for Ulkit is a CSS framework that have hundreds of beautiful components, templates, animations, effects and helpers inspired in Google Material Design. Everything fully responsive, compatible with different browsers.

- Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript.
- Available in npm install md-uikit

Real Estate Web Site and Portal

Monica Tejada Real Estate (06/2018)

Develop a portal and website for real estate on this platform the client can advertise properties available for purchase and sale.

- Website and Portal Frontend: React JS, react-redux, react-googlemaps.
- Backend: PHP, MySQL.

Expo Management Software

International Expo Arequipa (2017-2018-2019)

Developed a Progresive Web App and a portal to manage the registration, access control y marketing for the expositors.

- PWA: React JS, react-googlemaps.
- Portal Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, JQuery.
- Backend: PHP, MySQL.

Voting System

Catholic University of Santa Maria (07/2017)

Developer of the new Voting Web and Mobile applications for more than +12000 students. Project leader, responsible for the installation, configuration, and control during the electoral process.

- Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, D3.js.
- Backend: PHP, PostgreSQL.
- Mobile: Android SDK, QR Reader.
- API: PHP, PostgreSQL.

Online Admission Portal and Students Web Portal

Catholic University of Santa Maria (03/2017)

Developed a new Admission Portal to manage the admission process for +1500 applicants. This platform uses vision api for an image validation prior to registration.

- Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, Google Vision API. D3.js, FullCalendarJS, mPDF.
- Backend: ASP.net, C#, SQL Server 2008 R2.

EduGames Software

Max Uhle German School (12/2016)

Developed a Web Portal to provide educative resources for students, this platform aims to attract and evaluate students' abilities through interactive games and activities.

- Portal Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, Construct2.
- Backend: PHP, MySQL.

And more in: www.jeanvera.com